Paul Muldoon papers, 1939-2010
Emory University
- Printed material, circa 1940s-2005, Series 4; Boxes 35-37, 90-98 and OP 12-148, 168-172
  - Printed/bound material, circa 1940s-2004, Subseries 4.4; Boxes 36-37, 96-98 and OP 171-172
    - Falling to Sea Level, John Oliver Simon and Maureen Hurley, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Fault Lines, program for the American Conference for Irish Studies, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 15)
    - Faust II, flier for stage performance, Zurich, September 1997 (Box 96, Folder 16)
    - Festival: An Anthology of Irish Poets and Winners of Recent New England Poetry Prizes, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Field: Contemporary Poetry and Poetics, No. 34, Spring 1986 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Fran Fornyrdislag Till Fri Vers, September 24-26, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Harper's, September 1999, with forum conversation featuring Muldoon and four other poets (Box 96, Folder 17)
    - Harvard Magazine, January-February 1998 (Box 96, Folder 18)
    - Harvard Review, No. 8: Spring 1995, includes selections from Muldoon's Wow and Flutter (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Hertford College News (University of Oxford), Issue 3, Summer 1999 (Box 96, Folder 19)
    - Hjärnstorm, No. 33, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - The Hollins Critic, February 1996, with article on Muldoon by Harriet Zinnes (Box 96, Folder 20)
    - Honest Ulsterman, Issue 102, Autumn 1996, with an interview of Paul Muldoon and poetry by Nuala Ní Domhnaill (Box 96, Folder 21)
    - Ireland of the Welcomes, September-October 1996 [special issue on contemporary Irish Literature] (Box 96, Folder 22)
    - Jede Sekinde Leben, by Renate Axt (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Kalliope: A Journal of Women's Art, Vol. 6, no 3. (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - "Lawyers Committee for Human Rights--1997 Human Rights Award Dinner," program including poetry reading by Muldoon (Box 96, Folder 23)
    - Le Dindon Ligote, No. 3, March 1995 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Literature Alive, Vol. 3, No. 1, (June 1989) (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Look and Learn, November 23, 1963, including "The Wonderful Story of English Literature" (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Los Escarabajos Skalbaggarna, Ruben Aguilera (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Magma, Summer 2001, with poem written specifically for Magma by Muldoon, "Presiding Spirits" (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - The Malcolm Bradbury Memorial Trust, information pamphlet, circa 2001 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Martello, Spring 1984 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - May I Keep Company? by John J. Gorey C. SS. R, 1940's (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Modern Youth and Chastity, by Gerard Kelly (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Mukkula, 1997 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - National Poetry Day Celebrates Comic Verse, October 8, 1998, with poem, "Symposium," by Paul Muldoon (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Negative Capability and Cows, July 1996, with poems and translations by Paul Muldoon (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - The Newman Review, Vol. 3, No. 1 (Spring 1971), including Muldoon poem (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - New Writing, Volume 1: 0, 2004 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Nu kommer de!!! (Aarhus, Denmark), Danish literary publication with a feature on Muldoon, Eiléan Ní Chuilleanáin, Nuala Ní Dhomhnaill, and Medbh McGuckian (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Outlines, QUB journal, Hilary Term 1982 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - A Parcel of Poems for Ted Hughs on his sixty-fifth birthday, 17th August 1995, Faber and Faber, 1995 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - PBS Bulletin (Poetry Book Society), Number 162, Autumn 1994 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - PBS Bulletin (Poetry Book Society), Number 179, Winter 1998, with article on Muldoon's book, Hay (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - PBS Bulletin (Poetry Book Society), Number 195, Winter 2002, with feature article on Muldoon's Moy Sand and Gravel (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Pequod, No. 16/17, including section on "Thirteen Irish Poets" (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Peymata, November-December 1995, with translation of unidentified poem by Muldoon into Greek (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - Plague Country, by Philip Brady (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - P.N. Review, January-February 1998, with poetry by Paul Muldoon (Box 97, Folder 12)
    - Poesia (Milan), September 1997, with article on English-language poetry, references to Muldoon (Box 97, Folder 13)
    - Poesia (Milan), March 2000, with an article on Muldoon's book, Prince of the Quotidian (Box 97, Folder 14)
    - Poesia (Milan), November 2001, with translation of poem by Muldoon, "Moy Sand and Gravel," into Italian (Box 97, Folder 15)
    - Poesiealbum 146, Steffen Mensching (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Poetry, October-November 1997, eighty-fifth anniversary double issue featuring poem by Muldoon, "Apple Slump" (Box 97, Folder 16)
    - Poetry 1972, ed. By Damian Grant (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Poetry International Serie: Het dwingende verleden, Deriten moderne Ierse dichters (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Poetry News, Summer 1999 (Box 97, Folder 17)
    - Poetry Review, Winter 2002/2003 (Box 97, Folder 18)
    - Princeton, Spring 1998 (Box OP172)
    - Princeton alumni weekly, February 11, 1998, with cover story on Paul Muldoon (Box 97, Folder 19)
    - Rad Thu, Christian Desagulier, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Raritan, Vol. 9, No. 4, Spring, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - St. Patrick's College School Magazines, all ed. Patrick Beirne, Aidan Kilpatrick, and Aidan Rafferty: Celt, Cuff, and Familiar, with cuttings of several Muldoon contributions in Irish, all enclosed in black wrapping folder (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Sex education for older boys, Catholic Marriage Advisory Council, 1966, Aidan Pickering (Box 97, Folder 20)
    - Soho Square 1, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Stonefence Review, Vol. 1, No. 1 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Stonefence Review, Vol. 1, No. 2 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Studies in Literature 13, 1991 (Box 97, Folder 21)
    - Take Me Home Rickshaw, Translated by Farida Majod, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Terrenalis, Sergio Badilla (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - The Music of What Happens, Poems from the Listener, 1965-1980, ed. By Derwent May, pref. by Margaret Drabble (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Thirty Years of the Poetry Book Society, 1956-1986, ed. By Jonathan Barker (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Thumbscrew, number 4, spring 1996, with interview of Muldoon (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Thumbscrew, number 5, summer 1996 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Tijdschrift Voor Poesie/Revue de Poesie/Poetry Review, Jaargang 3. No. 3, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Translation Ireland, December 2000-January 2001 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Treasures of Pelham, Treasures of Pelham Committee, (Pelham, Massachusetts) 1968 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Troubadour Magazine, Princeton University, inaugural issue, Winter 2001 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - University of Oxford Annual Review 1998/1999, 1999 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - US 1 Worksheets, issue 34/35, with selections from Paul Muldoon's The Hopewell Haiku (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Virtue Without Terror 2 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Weltklang--nacht der poesie, Berlin Poetry Festival 2004, published by Edition diá, with poems by Muldoon translated into German (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Winter in the Tropics, Gene Ellis (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Writing Women, Vol. 4, No. 1 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Writing Women, Vol. 5, No. 1 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - The Yale Literary Magazine, volume XII, number 2, Fall 2000 (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - Yeats, Sligo and Ireland: Essays to Mark the 21st Yeats International Summer School, ed., by A. Norman Jeffares, Irish Literature Studies 6, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 24)
- Promotional material/Readings/Appearances, 1973-2005, Series 5; Boxes 38-41, 99-106 and OP 149-160, 173-174
  The series consists of material created to publicize and promote Muldoon and his work from 1973-2005. It includes materials from the British Broadcasting Company (BBC), posters featuring poems by Muldoon, and notices of readings given by Muldoon in the U.S. and elsewhere. The series also includes a number of items not directly related to Muldoon, including posters advertising the work of other writers, of literary festivals, and of musical events.
  Organized into three subseries: (5.1) British Broadcasting Corporation (BBC) materials, (5.2) Promotional materials, and (5.3) Readings and appearances.
  - British Broadcasting Corporation (BBC) materials, 1973-1985, Subseries 5.1; Box 38
    The subseries consists of promotional material from the British Broadcasting Corporation from 1973-1985, including director's packets, production materials, notes and schedules.
    - Script for The Rhyming Weavers by John Hewitt, produced by Muldoon (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Script for Dublin Indemnity, by John Morrow, produced by Muldoon (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Film Direction course materials (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Packet of director's materials for "The Love Scene from Translations," "Marilyn," "Movie Time," and "Magazine Programme" (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous television production materials, including several proposals and schedules (headed "Muldoon television" by Muldoon) (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - BBC Radio Teacher's Notes, Spring 1984 and Autumn 1985 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Arts Programme schedules, 1979-1984 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Address book, bound but no cover (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - BBC appointment books for 1973-1977 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - BBC Programme Week calendars 1978-1984 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Promotional materials, 1981-2003, Subseries 5.2; Box 39, 99-100 and OP 149-160, 173
    The subseries consists of general promotional materials for Muldoon from 1981-2003. Folders include posters, flyers, and pictures that publicize Muldoon and his writing.
    Arranged in chronological order, with oversized items last.
    - Promotional material
    - Poetry International, Rotterdam, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - National Poetry Competition in association with BBC Radio 3, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Ulster Museum press release: exhibition of portraits of Irish writers, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Whitbread book of the year, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Ecco Press catalogues, 1986-1988 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Yaddo annual report, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Poetry Society of America, calendar of events, 1989-1990 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - The 31st Yeats International Summer School, Sligo, Ireland, August 11-25, 1990 and The Yeats Theatre festival brochure, August 19, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Faber and Faber New Books, Stock List, and Children's Book list, 1990-1995 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - St. Mary's College Courier, Alumni Magazine (including interview with Paul Muldoon), Spring, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Writer's in Performance, Manhattan Theatre Club, 1991 (including a copy of Paul Muldoon's introduction for Adam Zagajewski and C. K. Williams and letter to Muldoon from reading organizer.) (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Chevrolet Celtic Classic Highland Games and Festival, Bethlehem, PA, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Writers in Performance, Manhattan Theatre Club brochure, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Modern Language Association Program, November, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Third Dublin International Writer's Festival, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - The Gallery Press New Books Stock List, Summer/Autumn, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - The Forward Prize for Poetry Announcement (Muldoon's The Annals of Chile on best collection shortlist), October 6, 1994. (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - "The Music of Edward T. Cone: A Celebratory Retrospective," Princeton University, November 11, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - The Aristeon Prize, European Literary and Translation Prize, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Poetry Society of America, calendar and awards, Fall 1994 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Poetry Book Society, T. S. Eliot Prize, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - "Itinerary for Dorothy, Jean, and Paul Muldoon," Ireland, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - A Reader's Companion to History, The Home Movie, a novel in verse by Craig Raine (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Folger Shakespeare Library brochure, 1994-1995 (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - McCarter Calendar News, late winter, 1994-1995 season, Princeton University arts (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Mimi Gerrard Dance Theatre, 30th Anniversary Retrospective, April 28-May 14, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - Poetry Book Society bulletins, Winter 1994 and Spring 1995 (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - Poetry Society of America newsletter, Spring 1995, No. 46 (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - The Gallery Press, Poetry, Plays and Fiction by Contemporary Irish Poets; New Books and Stock List, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 29)
    - Fighting Irish Studies, University of Notre Dame, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 30)
    - Tanglewood, 1995 (Darin Hagen's "The Waking Father" premiere featuring poems by Paul Muldoon) (Box 39, Folder 31)
    - Hopewell Haiku promotional brochure, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 32)
    - "A Sacred Place" play performed in conjunction with the Program in Theatre and Dance, Princeton University, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 33)
    - Ecco Press book covers for Paul Muldooon's Selected Poems, 1968-1986, and The Essential Byron (Box 39, Folder 34)
    - Faber and Faber Paul Muldoon book covers (Box 39, Folder 35)
    - Queen's University Festival, November 20, 1977 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Selected Poems, 1968-1986, 1993 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - The Annals of Chile, 1994 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Poetry Book Society, Paul Muldoon receiving the T.S. Eliot Prize, 1994 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - The Last Thesaurus, 1995-1998 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - New Selected Poems, 1968-1994, 1996 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Paul Muldoon, by Tim Kendall, 1996 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Trinity College Dublin, Summer School, 1996 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Unplugged, 1996 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - American Academy of Arts and Letters, Exhibition of Work by Newly Elected Members and Recipients of Honors and Awards, May 16-June 9, 1996 (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - Irish Times' Literature Prize for Poetry, October 1, 1997 (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - The Bangle, 1998 (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - The Faber Book of Beasts, 1998 (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - Hay, 1998 (Box 99, Folder 14)
    - Paul Muldoon: New Perspectives and Historical Sources, 1998 (Box 99, Folder 15)
    - Thumbscrew, Interview with Paul Muldoon, 1998 (Box 99, Folder 16)
    - Warwick Press, Announcement of Hopewell Haiku, 1998 (Box 99, Folder 17)
    - Publishers Weekly, June 29, 1998 (Box 99, Folder 18)
    - The College of New Jersey, Irish-American Society, November 12, 1998 (Box 99, Folder 19)
    - Poems, 1968-1998, 1998-2002 (Box 99, Folder 20)
    - The Birds, 1999 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Something Beginning with P, New Poems from Irish Poets, 1999 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Caedmon's Hymn, June 1, 1999 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Poetry in the New Yorker, 2000 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - To Ireland I, 2001-2002 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Exhibition for Festival at Queen's, 2002 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Reverse Flannery, 2002 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Moy Sand and Gravel, 2002-2003 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Promotional material, undated
    - Art from Conflict: A Selection of Belfast Artists and their Work, Crescent Arts Centre, Belfast, no date (Box 39, Folder 36)
    - "Images: Arts and the People in Northern Ireland," no date (Box 39, Folder 37)
    - Pelham, Massachusetts--Historical Materials, no date (Box 39, Folder 38)
    - Poet's House, New York, New York (brochure), no date (Box 39, Folder 39)
    - Stan Tracey Quartet Promotion for "The Poet's Suite," no date (Box 39, Folder 40)
    - "Take It Away" an Evening of Poetry and Jazz with the Billy White Trio, Candy Devine, and Catherine Gibson. Directed by Paul Muldoon, no date (Box 39, Folder 41)
    - Twin Elms Writer's Center Writiting Course, New Jersey, no date (Box 39, Folder 42)
    - University of Kentucky Announces a New Series in Irish Literature, History, and Culture. General Editor, Jonathan Allison, no date (Box 39, Folder 43)
    - Wake Forest University Press promotional materials, no date (Box 39, Folder 44)
    - The William McGonagall Award for Poetic License, winner: Paul Muldoon, no date (Box 39, Folder 45)
    - Miscellaneous promotional materials related to Paul Muldoon, no date (Box 39, Folder 46)
    - Miscellaneous promotional materials for events not directly related to Paul Muldoon, no date (Box 39, Folder 47)
    - Der Schmale Pfad in den Tiefen Norden, no date (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - Quoof, no date (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - Teach for America, no date (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - Oversized promotional material
    - Tara Mines educational poster on Hedgehogs with Muldoon's poem "Hedgehog" printed on it, with cover letter from Faber and Faber and holograph correction (probably not in Muldoon's hand) on poster (Box OP149)
    - Pencil sketch of Muldoon by Geraldine O'Reilly, 1990 (Box OP150)
    - Assorted promotional and artistic materials, including two posters from Wake Forest University Press, announcement of Maria; Simonds-Gooding exhibition, print of Paul Klee painting "They're Biting," announcement for Dingle Peninsula Festival of St. Brendan, and a Literary Map of Princeton, New Jersey (Box OP151)
    - Assorted promotional and artistic materials, continued, including Harvard College Library of reading by Muldoon and Seamus Heaney (four copies), music and lyrics of "Muldoon the Solid Man" by Edward Harrigan, 1974 Arts Council announcement of reading by James Simmons and Muldoon, announcement of reading by Pm at Mount Holyoke College, Morden Tower Poetry Reading announcement of reading by James Simmons and Muldoon, Steps Theater's "Poets in Person" evening with Muldoon and Douglas Dunn, and promotional photograph of Muldoon reading (Box OP152)
    - First Trust calendar, with Muldoon poem "Ma" printed on October 1996 (Box OP153)
    - Poetry International 1981 promotional poster with quote from Muldoon poem (Box OP154)
    - Evening Telegraph, June 16, 1904, with extensive holograph notes and "Muldoon" written at top (Box OP155)
    - "New Poetry from the United Kingdom," announcement for reading including Muldoon sponsored by the Library of Congress (Box OP156)
    - City of Boston Certificate of Recognition for Festival of Irish Poetry, signed by the Mayor, May 12, 1990 (Box OP157)
    - "Upstairs in a Tent," announcement for reading by Muldoon, John; Marrow, Deirdre Shannon, and Ciaran Carson (Box OP158)
    - Miscellaneous Ecco enclosures (Box OP159)
    - Miscellaneous Faber enclosures (Box OP160)
    - National Poetry Month poster, no date (Box OP173)
  - Readings and appearances, 1980-2005, Subseries 5.3; Boxes 40-41, 101-106 and OP 174
    The subseries consists of printed materials relating to events involving Muldoon from 1980-2005. Most of the events feature Muldoon poetry readings, but the subseries also includes workshops and classes led by Muldoon, poetry competitions judged by Muldoon, and various events that Muldoon attended but at which he did not speak.
    - Reading set lists (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - "A Sense of Ireland" London Festival of the Irish Arts, February 1-March 15, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Other Worlds: A Reader's and Writer's Guide to the Galaxy, December 1980-January 1981 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - International Poetry Festival, Rotterdam, June 1981 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Book Project Festival, Dublin, November 9-28, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Bilingual Poetry Festival, Samhain Féile Filíochta, November 24, 1981 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Swarthmore College, March 17, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Newcastle Festival, October, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - The Poetry Society and Faber and Faber: Reading to Celebrate the publication of Michael Hoffmann's Acrimony and Paul Muldoon's Selected Poems, 1968-1983 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - "Poetry at Five": 21st Belfast Festival at Queens, November 9-26, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - "Paul Muldoon Reads His Poetry" Arts Committee, University of Surrey, Guilford, February 13,1984 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - The Yeats Society, Yeats International Summer School, August 11-25, 1984 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - "Northern Ireland: the Mind of a Community in Crisis," The College of William and Mary, September 20-22, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Cheltenham Literature Festival, October 14, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Oxford Poetry Festival, October 25-28, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Writer's Tours, Northwest Arts, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - "Kavanagh's Yearly: A Celebration of the Poet and His Work," in Carrickmacross and Inniskeen, Co. Monaghan, November 22-24, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Cheltenham Literature Festival, October 5-9, 1986 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Judith E. Wilson Visiting Fellow Poetry Reading, Cambridge, October 10, 1986 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Siol Phad Raig: Tongues, Live Poetry and Music, Irish Arts Festival, London, February 19-April 6, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - The Academy of American Poets, and Evening of New Irish Poetry, April 21, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - An Evening of Irish Poetry, the Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum Auditorium, Sponsored by the Academy of American Poets, April 21, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Columbia University, Poetry reading and teaching materials, 1987-1988 (Box 40, Folder 20a)
    - "The Literary Imagination," Department of English, McGill University, October, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - The Five College Irish Studies Committee: Paul Muldoon and Symposium on Contemporary Irish Poetry, University of Massachusetts at Amherst, October 27-29, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Writers in Performance, Manhattan Theatre Club, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - American Conference for Irish Studies, Onondaga Community College, April 12-15, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - "Soundscapes, 1989" at the Penine Hart Gallery, New York City: Paul Muldoon and Jean Hanff Korelitz, December 16, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - New York City Poetry Calendar, December 1989 (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - Howard County Poetry and Literature Society, Twelfth Annual Evening of Irish Music and Poetry, Featuring Paul Muldoon, February 16, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - Ireland in Canada: The Canadian Association for Irish Studies, March 7-11, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - Conference on Irish Literature and Culture, University of Notre Dame, March 23-24, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - Conflict Resolution Through the Arts: Focus on Ireland, Ward-Nasse Gallery, New York, March 1-25, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 30)
    - The Poetry Center of the 92nd Street Y: Irish Literature Festival, May 16, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 31)
    - 21st Poetry International, Rotterdam, June 16-23, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 32)
    - A Festival of Poetry from Around the World, South Bank Centre, September 27-October 6, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 33)
    - Cheltenham Literature Festival, October 13-21, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 34)
    - "Irish Week" Presented by Irish Newfoundland Association, March 9-18, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 35)
    - The Poetry Society of America, the National Arts Club, and the W.H. Auden Society tribute to W.H. Auden, April 4, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 36)
    - Cuirt International Poetry Festival, Galway, Ireland, April 11-14, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 37)
    - An Evening of Irish Poetry with Seamus Heaney, Derek Mahon, and Paul Muldoon, Swarthmore College, April 23, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 38)
    - Fifth International Poetry Days at Malmo, Sweden, May 21-26, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 39)
    - "Madoc: A Mystery," Reading at Micawber Books, Princeton, New Jersey, June 7, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 40)
    - Callanwolde Poet's Weekend Workshop, Amy Clampitt and Paul Muldoon Atlanta, Georgia, July 13-14, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 41)
    - Poetry and Literature, Library of Congress, Washington D.C., December 5, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 42)
    - "Northern Ireland: Cultural Counterpoint," State University of New York at Binghampton, January 24-26, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 43)
    - Poetry-in-the-Round Presents: A Poet's Tribute to Walt Whitman, Camden, New Jersey, March 26, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 44)